- "Previously on The Mentalist..."
- "Yeah, Lena's on a short list"
for a position in the Commerce
Department in D.C. so we're celebrating.
It's not a done deal yet.
I have to be confirmed,
and that could take months.
What can you tell me
about Rio Bravo station?
- "I don't think I want to go to D.C."
- Why?
Because you're gonna be
asked questions
and if any of those questions
involve Rio Bravo
then you need to be able to say
that you don't know anything about it.
"Hi, folks.
Welcome to Alamo Brewhouse."
"Christine will show you
to your table."
Hey, guys. Come on and join us.
We have a great Chilean sea bass
today for you guys.
Sit you right over here.
D.E.A.! Search warrant!
- Come on, let me see some hands!
- Put your hands on the table!
D.E.A.!
"Police! Police!"
- Down on the ground now!
- Head down on the ground now!
Hands behind your head!
- Sit!
- What's going on?
We have a warrant to search
these premises for illegal narcotics.
Narcot...
This is a restaurant.
Sir, read the warrant.
Let me do my job, okay?
You want a meeting with me?
Let's go talk in my office.
- Oh, you wanna go to your office?
- Let's talk.
Yeah, let's do that.
Let's start there.
What do you got, Orosco?
Yeah, we searched the office,
dining room, freezer.
K9 went through everything.
We got nothing.
- Okay, search again.
- Okay.
Don't walk away.
I'm talking to you.
Mr. Korbell, we are going
to finish our search.
This is harassment!
The more you interfere,
the longer it's gonna take.
Who's going to clean
this place up? Huh?
- I'm talking to you, bitch!
- Hey! Hey!
Okay.
Don't talk to my agent
that way.
Okay, easy.
Gonzalez.
Pack up and get out of here.
I'm watching you, pal.
Little dog, put your hands on me?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Bill Peterson.
There he is right there.
- Hey!
- Hey.
Dennis. You look good.
- You lost weight.
- Oh, yeah, a little bit. Thanks.
- How's Lena?
- She's in D.C.
Big things doing.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, good for her.
So, Dennis Abbott is handling
the After Action report
on my team's failed raid
on Alamo Brewhouse.
Yeah, well, D.C. asked.
You know, they want someone
outside of D.E.A.
Look, I don't want this
to be awkward.
Why?
Because when you worked for me,
you were barely shaving?
Yeah. Something like that.
It's been a long time
since Rio Bravo station.
You've come up in the world.
- Still, we did some good work.
- Yes, we did.
So, look, I am gonna
need to talk to your people
- and take a look at the files.
- Have at it.
Alamo Brewhouse
was just bad luck.
And you didn't find
any drugs?
Different day,
we would have.
I wanna start with the agent
who led the raid, Gonzalez.
You know, I understand that the restaurant
owner filed a complaint against him.
Gonzo got a little overheated,
you know.
He's on administrative leave.
I'll... I'll get you
his home address.
Dennis, I'm gonna wanna take a look
at that report of yours before it goes in.
Well, you know,
that's not how we do things, Bill.
A lot of people in this agency
got their gunsights set
for ol' Bill Peterson.
I need to know if you're handing 'em
any bullets.
Well, I'm sorry.
My hands are tied.
When I was your boss at Rio Bravo,
I had your back.
You're telling me
you don't have mine now?
Is that how you wanna play this?
Come on.
I'm just looking for a little
professional courtesy.
I'll see what I can do, Bill.
All right.
Thanks.
"I don't understand why you have to
write the damn report."
Oh, it's nothing.
I'll write it, D.C. will ignore it
and we'll get on with our lives.
- "How are you, baby?"
- Good.
I just had lunch with a senator.
I'm meeting with the chair
of the energy and commerce
committee in an hour.
"It's exciting."
I wish I were there.
- "I'll call you tonight, okay?"
- I love you.
I love you, too.
FBI!
Agent Gonzalez, are you in here?
Abbott said it was the death
of a D.E.A. agent.
By the way,
keep tomorrow night open.
- Why would it be closed?
- Your birthday.
Oh, that. Yes.
I already told everybody at work...
no songs, no cake, no gifts.
- Good. Thank you.
- Except me.
- Oh, you have a gift for me?
- It's a surprise.
- A surprise?
- That's right.
You think you can keep a secret
from me for that long?
I don't think I can. I know I can.
I admire your confidence.
So, Vega, I've got tickets
to that Blues festival
and I was wondering...
Not "Vega." Michelle.
Michelle, I've got tickets,
and I was...
Hey.
Hi.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- So Michelle...
- Abbott wants us. Caught a case.
O-Okay. Great.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Okay.
Good morning, everyone.
This is Bill Peterson,
San Antonio D.E.A.
Our victim's name
is Darrell Gonzalez.
He's been with the D.E.A.
for seven years.
Served in Afghanistan
before that.
I want you all to know how much
I appreciate your help.
We're gonna get the pigs
who did this.
We understand how hard it is
to lose somebody.
We will extend every courtesy
to you.
Every courtesy?
That's the Sosa cartel tag.
Looks like they're trying
to send a message.
Gonzo had just led a raid
on a restaurant
that was distributing
Sosa narcotics.
And it was owned
by this man.
Steven Korbell.
How does a restaurant owner
become a drug dealer?
He used to manage a hotel
in Mexico City
that was owned
by the Sosas.
That's when he began working
with them.
In the raid that Gonzalez led,
they didn't find anything.
Why would Korbell order a hit
after an unsuccessful raid?
I mean, it just calls
more attention to him.
Exactly.
The animal that escapes a snare doesn't
necessarily go after the poacher.
Okay, everyone, we can ask
these questions in San Antonio.
So, saddle up.
What does this guy Peterson
have on you?
Why do you ask?
Because you're acting like
he has something on you.
He doesn't.
Okay.
- Gonzalez's desk?
- Yeah, we were neighbors.
Man, he used to listen
to the worst music.
Smooth jazz.
Let's see.
Alamo Brewhouse file.
- Yeah.
- That's thorough.
Yeah, he didn't talk computers.
He kept a hard copy
on everything...
financial records
witness interviews,
surveillance photos.
My kind of people.
You mind if I take a look?
- Dig in.
- Thank you.
How long had Agent Gonzalez
been investigating
the Alamo Brewhouse?
- Months.
- Gonzo was relentless.
He slept here on the couch
half the week.
Agent Bordick, you were
the analyst working with him?
What are you implying?
I'm implying you were
the analyst working with him.
We had this one right.
That restaurant was a front
and we must've just missed
the supply re-up.
This wasn't your
first time coming up empty.
Your team's had other misses.
How long have the two of you
been out of the Academy?
- An hour?
- Whoa.
- Easy, Jeff.
- It's okay, Agent Orosco.
We'd be happy to send you
our CVs if you like.
Did you have any contact
with Gonzalez
in the days following the raid,
after he was on leave?
No. No, but that wasn't unusual.
Do you know what he was doing?
Knowing Gonzo,
he was probably obsessing
over why that raid went south.
Excuse me. That's the front
of the restaurant, right?
Yeah. Those are
the surveillance photos.
Taken over a few days?
- No, we staked it out for a few weeks.
- Excellent.
You know where the owner
of the restaurant is?
He's here. He's talking to Cho
and one of the D.E.A. agents.
What's he doing?
Mr. Korbell is a community pillar.
He sponsors chili cook-offs
and youth baseball teams.
He's not a killer.
He's got a hell of a P.R. Department,
I'll give him that.
Where were you yesterday
from 8:00 a.m. to 3:00 p.m.?
In Dallas. I had business.
Produce evidence of a crime,
gentlemen.
So far you've done a bang-up job
of the opposite.
- Hi. Patrick Jane. FBI.
- What the hell is this?
- Hey, Cho.
- Hi, Jane.
- Korbell?
- Yeah.
Very important question.
What time does your restaurant open?
Noon.
So you'll be opening
in a little under an hour.
If I'm not wasting
my time here, yeah.
- These two are free to go.
- Hey!
Have a lovely afternoon.
Thanks for your time.
- You can't do this, man.
- Yes, he can. You can go.
Hey.
- What the hell is this, man?
- Easy, tiger.
FBI is sending a team in to raid
that restaurant this afternoon.
If we find drugs, we wanna make sure
Korbell's there.
- Why didn't anybody tell us?
- What did I just do?
Hey.
You're never gonna believe
what this guy just told me.
Care to tell me
why we're here?
Of course.
In three minutes.
- How do you know Peterson?
- I worked for him.
A long time ago.
- You must've been very green.
- Oh, you have no idea.
Agent Peterson.
Were your ears burning?
Dennis. What's up?
- You're raiding Alamo Brewhouse?
- No.
This one here told my people
you're sending in a strike team.
I did. Sorry.
- That was a lie.
- What?
A fib. An untruth.
I made it up.
Have a seat. I'll explain.
Do either of you notice the difference
from this photo to this photo?
Where's Waldo?
There's a light bulb on the sign
that's off in one photo
and on in the other.
So they had
a broken light bulb.
But then it's on again here...
And off...
And on.
It's a signal.
When the light is on,
they're selling drugs.
When it's off, they're not.
This photo was taken the day
of your raid.
You notice how the light is off?
And that's why you guys
didn't find anything.
They weren't selling.
But why that day, huh?
Was it just bad luck?
Here we are.
12:00 on the dot.
Oh no.
The green light is on today.
I turned it on.
But what do you think
Korbell is gonna do
when he thinks
another raid is coming?
"And here you go."
Wait a minute.
- How could Korbell know that?
- He has an inside source.
Someone from D.E.A.
And if I figured it out,
Gonzalez did.
That's what got him killed.
What are you saying?
That someone on your team
is a killer.
So, we're looking for a cop
that killed a cop.
Gonzalez must have figured out
there was a mole.
The mole killed him
before he could go public.
Whoever it is,
he's been at it a while.
There have been a half a dozen
busted raids in the past two years.
Peterson's explained them all away...
bad Intel, tactical mistakes.
In hindsight, it had to have
been an inside man.
So for now
we don't rule out anyone.
It could be any one
of Peterson's agents.
- That's 30 suspects.
- 31. You forgot Peterson.
Bill Peterson doesn't have
much of a bedside manner
but he's not a traitor.
I thought we couldn't
rule anyone out.
Abbott's right.
Peterson's not a suspect.
Good. So, we'll,
just dig down into his team.
Personal reviews, bank records.
Anything that points to a motive.
Ego, revenge.
What? You disagree?
Well, they're all poorly paid
government employees.
You're not gonna have to dig
too deep to find motive.
- You have a better idea?
- Maybe.
But first, I need someone
to run an errand for me.
Back at the D.E.A.
what were you and Orosco
saying to each other?
Oh, he was apologizing
for his partner being a jerk.
I said it was fine.
"You don't speak Spanish?"
I speak at a ninth-grade level.
I can say "grandmother"
and "hall pass."
- Do you speak any other languages?
- I'm fluent in pig Latin.
- I'm not really sure that counts.
- Listen, I wanted...
Vega, I need you to do something.
But first, a question.
Uh, we shoot new pictures
for the I.D. badges every year.
Does every federal agency do that?
- I think so.
- Excellent.
I need you to go back
to San Antonio.
I need you to get all photo I.D.s
for Peterson's D.E.A. team
for the past three years.
We just got back
from San Antonio.
I know. No rest for the weary
crimefighter.
- See you when I get back.
- Yeah.
- Abbott.
- "Dennis."
I'm in Austin. Like to talk,
if you got a minute.
Sure. Come by the office.
Actually, I'd prefer talking
outside your office.
"Mind meeting me
at Graham Plaza?"
Evening, Bill.
You want a drink?
- Club soda. Thanks.
- Another one.
A hell of a thing to know
that one of your people
betrayed you.
Killed a colleague.
A friend.
Yeah, it's hard, I know.
You didn't tell
your team anything?
No. They think it's an investigation
of a cartel murder.
Well, my people
are the best, Bill.
We'll get this guy.
I'm sure you will.
When you do,
I need to share the collar.
- What do you mean?
- I want credit for the arrest.
We'll come up
with something I did...
something vital to the
investigation, you know.
So you want me
to lie for you.
I told you, I have enemies.
They find out one of my people
was working for the cartel
they'll take me to town
unless I do something.
I need to be part
of the solution.
You have been asleep
at the wheel.
One of your people
has been in bed
with the Sosas for two years,
and you didn't see it.
Now you want me
to cover your ass?
We should be having a discussion
about your resignation.
We've all done things
we're not proud of, Dennis...
things we'd like
kept quiet.
So you're gonna hang Rio Bravo
over my head
unless I play along.
I wish it was just you.
Lena's confirmation is coming up
in a couple of weeks, right?
Rio Bravo could be
a real problem there, too.
I need this, Dennis.
Keep me posted.
You ready to get out of here?
- I think I'm gonna stick around.
- Okay.
Any guesses about your present?
Or have you given up?
Does it weigh more or less
than 3 1/2 pounds?
Why 3 1/2 pounds?
- Because.
- Less.
- Is it made of Kryptonite?
- No.
Is it something that I would
wear on a cold winter's day?
No.
That is my guess.
Promise me you will not open it
till tomorrow night.
- You are so bluffing. Aren't you?
- See you later.
I'm guessing by your look
that you just talked to Peterson.
I'm listening.
I worked for him
about ten years ago
when he was running a task force
on the border.
Rio Bravo station.
We were working
with the Mexican police
trying to do something
about the cartels.
- Tough work.
- It was war.
The Zeta cartel would send their
men out dressed like soldiers.
They would wait for a bus
to come through
stop it, force all
the passengers off
and shoot them.
All of them.
Just so they didn't work
for another cartel.
There were bodies everywhere.
Men, women, children...
Scattered all over the road
like trash.
Yeah, it's... it's no picture
that anyone should have in their head.
One day I was sitting
on a Zeta safe house...
just watching
who came and went.
Gathering Intel.
And I saw this...
- Zeta commander walk out.
- Dressed in a military uniform.
And I knew what he was gonna do.
I couldn't call the local police
because they were terrified of the Zetas.
I couldn't arrest him.
So I sat there, thinking...
I don't know...
maybe three seconds.
I got out of my car
I walked across the street,
and I shot him.
You...
You did the right thing.
I don't know.
But no buses were stopped that night.
And the next day
I quit the Rio Bravo station.
Did Peterson know
what you had done?
He guessed.
The death of a commander
hit the news.
Tons of speculation
on who killed him and...
Peterson knew
where I was when it happened.
And now he's threatening you
to do what he says.
Peterson can end my career.
I can go to prison.
But it's not just about me.
Any mention of this could end things
for Lena before it even starts.
Well, you can't let him do it.
I appreciate the thought.
How do we stop him?
I'm not sure.
Yet.
But when I know,
I'll tell you the answer.
- Hey, can you help me with something?
- Sure.
Abbott asked me to look
into Korbell's records
see how he's communicating
with his contact on Peterson's team.
I've looked at Korbell's
phone, e-mails, texts.
Nothing jumps out.
They're too smart to use
something that easy to get into.
They must have been making
contact somehow.
Check his day-to-day.
What was Korbell looking
at on the web?
Based on the sites he visits
he's a Houston fan.
He buys a lot of protein powder.
He's into Persian longhairs.
The cats?
- Yeah.
- No way.
Way. He spends a lot of time
on a Persian longhair website.
I've read his file.
There is no way Korbell is into cats.
He's too macho
too desperate for approval.
Must have been going there
for something.
Maybe they're communicating
through the message boards.
Nobody would look
there first.
I'll check it out.
- I got the I.D. pictures.
- Thank you.
The past three years for each person
on Peterson's team.
30 in total.
Most recent pictures on top.
You're a marvel, Vega.
Well done.
What are you looking at?
Their eyes.
- Windows to the soul.
- You can't be serious.
Good call, Vega.
Really, what are you looking at?
Well, I don't wanna ruin the surprise
but since you're interested
there may be something
you can help me with.
Requires some bravado
which should be right up your alley.
- Help you with what?
- A little something to catch a killer.
- You want me to help you with a trick.
- Well, if that's what you wanna call it.
Problem?
Speak your mind, soldier.
It's just...
I very much appreciate being
a part of this team, sir.
You get results.
- I respect that.
- Thank you. But?
The things you ask people
to do...
it's...
It's not what I thought working
for the FBI would be like.
- At all.
- No.
And, uh, more importantly
you wonder if your father
would approve.
Sometimes.
He was strict.
37 years in the military
makes you a stickler for the rules.
I'm sure he was.
And a good father.
And you're proof of that.
But I can't tell you what your father
would approve of.
That's for you to decide.
- Sir?
- Yes, Vega?
What do you want me to do?
Well, when I'm finished here,
I'll tell you.
Sure.
Thank you.
- Abbott.
- Dennis, any progress?
- Some.
- Don't make me chase you down.
What's going on?
We're gathering information.
"Let me know as soon
as you got something."
"Don't hold out on me."
That will not go well.
- Making progress?
- Yes, actually.
Got something. Korbell was trading
messages with his contact
on Peterson's team
through a cat blog.
What was in the messages?
Coded language
about D.E.A. investigations.
The first letter of each word
spells the message.
So, for instance...
"Reactive allergies
in de-clawed animals?"
"Try 4 preventative measures."
That spells "Raid at 4pm."
It's actually pretty cool.
- Do we know who Korbell was dealing with?
- No.
Whoever it is has covered his tracks
with proxy servers and VPNs.
- Whatever they are.
- But here's something interesting.
As of yesterday,
he suddenly stopped posting.
There are no new messages.
- He's getting ready to run.
- Maybe he's just laying low.
Well, a poker player that stops betting
isn't laying low.
He's cashing in.
Well, if he's about to rabbit,
then we better move quickly.
It's perfect.
Call San Antonio.
Tell them there's been
a breakthrough in the case.
Have them gather up these ten agents
and I'll go talk to them in two hours.
Everybody's here.
You needn't worry.
- I'm not worried.
- Good.
Vega, you're on.
"Just stay relaxed.
You'll be just fine."
Thank you, sir.
Let's go.
Agent Peterson.
You're one of Abbott's people, right?
I'll be down to whatever
he's doing in a minute.
Actually, sir...
You're under arrest.
I'm what?
Thank you for coming.
Could you all take a seat
up front here, please?
Thank you.
I know you're wondering
why you're here.
The answer to that is simple...
one of you killed
Darrell Gonzalez.
- And...
- What?
I'm gonna tell you who
in about five minutes.
Agents Cho and Lisbon
will come through the aisles.
We're asking you
to give up your guns.
You got to be kidding me.
We'll return the weapons
when this is over.
If you're innocent,
there's no problem.
If there's a killer in the room
we don't wanna risk a gun fight.
We don't want anyone to get hurt.
I'm afraid I have to insist.
One of you is working
with the Sosa cartel
and betrayed your team.
If you're not interested
in knowing who that person is
by all means, keep your guns.
Thank you.
Question...
have any of you
recently inherited
some money from a deceased
parent or grandparent?
I'm not talking
about a little bit.
A pile, enough to make a difference.
Raise your hands, please.
Don't be shy.
I'm very sorry for your losses.
None of you killed
Darrell Gonzalez.
You can move to the back
of the room, please.
Thank you.
What does an inheritance
have to do with who killed Gonzalez?
That is a good question.
But I am the one
asking those right now.
Now, is there anyone here in a relationship
with someone from the beauty field?
Yeah. My husband runs a couple
of styling salons.
How long have you been together?
- A year.
- Congratulations.
I'm very happy for you.
You didn't kill Darrell Gonzalez.
Would you move to the back
of the room, please?
Anyone here get divorced
in the past three years?
Yes, law enforcement...
tough on the home life.
On the plus side,
you didn't kill Gonzalez.
- Back you go, please.
- Oh. Wow.
You think one of us are in bed
with the Sosas?
- That's crazy.
- Really. Why would we do that?
Money, I assume.
But I, I don't care about the motive.
I'm interested in what happened
after one of you became a traitor.
I looked at your I.D. pictures
for the last few years.
All ten of you have improved
your appearance
most noticeably by sprucing up
your hair.
Some of you because
you inherited money
others because you're back
in the dating scene.
Are you seriously saying
that one of us is the killer
because we got
a better haircut?
A killer, no. A traitor, yes.
Whoever sold out to the Sosas made bank
and got a big ego boost.
When you have a good secret,
it makes you feel important.
If you're so sure,
which one of us is it?
- Well, that's the question, isn't it?
- Jane.
- Just a minute, Vega.
- I found the killer.
It's Bill Peterson.
You're seriously doing this.
I was certain it was gonna be
one of the other three agents.
Are we sure about this?
Wylie found a link through the cat blog
to an offshore account in Belize.
It was hidden under aliases and shells
but he traced it back to Peterson.
3.2 million bucks.
You're accusing me...
get your people in line!
Take him out of here.
Abbott... You think I'm gonna
forget about this, huh?
Is that what you think?!
You have evidence
against Agent Peterson?
You can pick up your firearms
on the way out. We're done here.
- Bordick.
- Yeah?
You look like you're in a hurry.
What's the rush?
Nothing.
I mean none.
You got a go-bag in your trunk,
don't you?
What are you talking about?
You killed Darrell Gonzalez.
Where are you headed?
The Gulf?
Airport?
Why would I be going
to the Gulf?
You killed Darrell Gonzalez.
So you thought you were
gonna get away?
Excuse me?
When we arrested Peterson
you thought you had time to escape.
- But I know what you did.
- What?
- You killed Darrell Gonzalez.
- No. Peterson did.
You guys said so.
You arrested him.
It was you. I'm not letting
you alone until I prove it.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I am going to tail you every day
until you're in cuffs.
I don't care how long it takes.
I am gonna put you
behind bars.
Lisbon.
This is Abbott.
Cho.
Blanks.
We found your go-bag.
Yeah, quite the trip
you were planning.
Fake passport,
Croatian Kunas.
Hey, Lisbon, does Croatia
have an extradition treaty with the U.S.?
I don't believe they do.
We also found the tracking program
you installed on Gonzalez's computer.
He'd suspected a mole.
It was only a matter of time
before he latched on to you.
So, why did you start working
for the Sosas?
Why betray your team?
My team?
I've been at D.E.A.
for six years.
You know how many times my "team"
has passed me over for promotions?
So you wanted to show them
how smart you are?
No, wait a minute.
He couldn't be that smart.
I mean, we caught you.
Took you years.
That whole time, I was tipping off dealers
ruining busts, stashing payoffs.
I was the most powerful guy
in that building.
Nobody knew.
So who's the smart one?
Let's get this smart man
a nice jail cell.
"We found enough evidence
in Orosco's apartment"
"to arrest Korbell and several
of his employees."
Korbell's gonna flip
against the Sosa cartel.
Feels like a win,
all in all.
You humiliated me
in front of my people!
You perp-walked me
through my own office!
We had to make Orosco feel like
he had a chance to get away.
You were the misdirection.
It's not the best part,
but you played it adequately.
You were supposed to tell me
what you were doing.
We couldn't do that.
You would have blown the shot.
I mean, obviously.
Look, I'm sorry, Bill.
Really, I am.
I was supposed to get the credit!
We had a deal!
There was no deal, Bill.
Just a crazy idea you had
in your head.
You're done, Abbott.
It's over for you and your wife.
I'm gonna see to that.
Okay. I've been patient.
I've been polite.
Not anymore. Take it back.
What?!
Take back your little threat
and apologize to my friend here.
Why?
This display, this tantrum...
it isn't about anger, is it?
It's about fear.
Fear? Of what?
That we weren't too far off about
you keeping a stash of dirty money
and that with enough time,
we will find it.
Give my best to Lena.
- Are you sure about this?
- Absolutely.
We have him
right where we want him.
- No, I heard you were awesome down there.
- Really?
Oh, because I felt like I was
gonna throw up the whole time.
Lisbon said you nailed arresting Peterson.
Like a pro.
- Well, it was actually fun.
- Yeah?
I didn't think it would be,
but, uh, it was.
- Oh, God.
- What?
It's Bordick,
from San Antonio D.E.A.
He's... asking me out.
Fortunately, I can honestly
tell him I have no interest.
I am so not into that right now.
I just wanna focus on work.
Sure.
- Know what I mean?
- Yeah. Totally.
Me too.
I am taking these files
down to admin.
But will you be here later?
Almost certainly.
See you.
The lights are a nice touch.
- Happy Birthday.
- Thank you.
Make a wish.
And here is your gift.
Open it.
Lisbon.
The one and only.
From the CBI.
- You kept the pieces.
- Yeah.
- Looks pretty nice, doesn't it?
- It's perfect.
I'm speechless.
It's...
You really didn't know
what it was?
Yeah, you can see for yourself.
You really didn't know?
I'm genuinely surprised.
This is...
This is such a beautiful gift.
Thank you so much.
I'm amazed.
Bravo.
Are you sure you're
not just pretending
you didn't know what it was
to make me feel better?
Because you don't have to make
me feel better.
No, come on, please.
Lisbon, just take the compliment.
Fine.
- Cheers.